I HAVEN'T BEEN SUCCESSFUL.
THIS TIME I'M TRYING TO CONTROL
MY SENSE OF SELF-RIGHTEOUSNESS
AND JUDGMENT ON THE OTHERS.
>> I'M BACK BECAUSE THIS IS ONE
MORE SHOT FOR ME TO PROVE TO
EVERYBODY THAT I CAN OWN THIS
GAME AND THAT IT CAN BE DONE
WITH HONOR AND INTEGRITY.
>> I'VE BEEN THE GUY THAT'S ABLE
TO CLIMB COCONUT TREES AND HUNT
FISH.
I'VE ALSO BEEN REALLY STRONG IN
CHALLENGES, BUT I DON'T THINK I
HAD THE BEST STRATEGY.
>> GO, OZZY!
>> THIS TIME I'M MORE MATURE AND
I'VE LEARNED FROM MY MISTAKES.
I NEED REDEMPTION BECAUSE I FEEL
LIKE I JUST HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO
LOCK MY HANDS ON THE MILLION
DOLLARS.
I'VE ALMOST BEEN THERE A FEW
TIMES AND I JUST HAVEN'T BEEN
ABLE TO FINISH.
>> Jeff: THIS IS REDEMPTION
ISLAND ARENA WHERE THEIR BATTLE
WILL BEGIN.
THEL BE COMPETING AGAINST EACH
OTHER AND A NEW GROUP OF
CASTAWAYS, EACH WITH THEIR OWN
STORY TO TELL.
>>IM BY FAR THE MOST "SURVIVOR"
SAVVY PLAYER EVER TO PLAY THE
GAME.
I'VE NEVER MISSED A SINGLE
EPISODE.
AT LAW SCHOOL I WON A
PRIZE-WINNING ESSAY ON
"SURVIVOR."
>> I DON'T HAVE A GREAT
BACKGROUND IN OUTDOORSMAN
ACTIVITIESES, BUT I'M NATIVE
AMERICAN.
SO I'M HOPING THAT SOMEWHERE IN
MY ANCESTRAL BACKGROUND, THE
GREAT SPIRITS WILL IMPART ON ME
SOME WISDOM.
>> I'M 51 YEARS OLD.
I OWN MY OWN RANCH IN UTAH,
CATTLE RANCH.
IF YOU DIDN'T TRAIN BEFORE YOU
GOT HERE, I MEAN, IF YOU DIDN'T
RUN, IF YOU DIDN'T LEARN HOW TO
BUILD A FIRE, YOU MIGHT AS WELL
SPIT IN THE WIND.
>> I'M 44 YEARS OLD.
I'M A FUNERAL DIRECTOR
MORTICIAN.
I HAVE FOUR CHILDREN.
BEING THE MOTHER THEY AM, I'M
GOING TO HAVE MY EYES AND MY
EARS OPEN.
YOU THINK I'M ASLEEP.
I'M NOT ASLEEP.
I'LL BE NOSY AS HELL.
>> I AM RUSSELL HANTZ'S NEPHEW.
IT'S LIKE BEING RELATED TO
HITLER, BUT I DON'T THINK
HITLER'S NEPHEW WAS RUNNING
AROUND SAYING, "HEY, I'M
HITLER'S NEPHEW."
I CAME OUT HERE TO CHANGE THE
COURSE OF THE HANTZ FAMILY'S
NAME.
>> Jeff: IT IS THE ULTIMATE
CHALLENGE-- 18 STRANGERS FORCED
TO WORK TOGETHER TO CREATE A NEW
SOCIETY WHILE BATTLING THE
ELEMENTS AND EACH OTHER.
THEY MUST LEARN TO ADAPT OR
THEY'LL BE VOTED OUT.
IN THE END, ONLY ONE WILL REMAIN
TO CLAIMANT MILLION-DOLLAR
PRIZE.
39 DAYS, 18 PEOPLE, ONE
SURVIVOR.
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
and Ford.
Drive one.
>> Jeff: COME ON UP, GUYS.
WELCOME TO "SURVIVOR: SOUTH
PACIFIC"
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
YOU HAVE ALL BEEN DIVIDED INTO
TWO TEENS BUT YOUR TRIBES ARE
NOT YET COMPLETE.
TWO MORE PEOPLE ARE GOING TO BE
JOINING YOU IN THIS GAME.
LET'S BRING THEM IN.
>> OH, MAN.
>> OH, MY GOD.
WHO IS IT GOING TO BE?
>> I'M A LITTLE BIT NERVOUS TO
SEE WHO IT IS.
>> LET'S HOPE IT'S NOT RUSSELL.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS!
THAT WOULD SUCK.
>> I HOPE IT'S NOT RUSSELL.
>> ME, EITHER.
>> THE LADY NEXT TO ME, SHE
GOES, "OH, MY GOD, I HOPE IT'S
NOT RUSSELL HANTZ."
I WILL NEVER, EVER TELL THEM MY
LAST NAME.
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO THINK I'M A
HANTZ.
AS LONG AS I KEEP MY SHIRT ON
BECAUSE THIS TATTOO SAYS "LITTLE
HANTZ" ON IT AND THIS TATTOO
SAYS "HANTZ" ON IT.
>> HEY, SO WE'RE EXCITED FOR
THESE PEOPLE.
>> OH, YEAH?
>> YEAH, OH, ABSOLUTELY.
THEY WERE PART OF THE FAMILY.
>> OZZY.
>> OH, OZZY'S NUTS.
HE CAN BE ON OUR TEAM.
HE CAN FISH LIKE A SON OF A GUN.
>> IT'S COACH.
>> IT'S FREAKING COACH.
>> IT IS COACH.
>> THE HELICOPTER COMES IN, AND
ALL OF A SUDDEN YOU SEE COACH
AND YOU SEE OZZY, AND OF COURSE
OFF THE BAT YOU'RE LIKE OZZY!
>> OZZY!
ALL RIGHT!
( APPLAUSE ).
>> THIS GUY CAN CLAIM, HE CAN
FISH.
HE'S FAST.
HE'S JUST AN AMAZING ATHLETE,
SOMEBODY YOU WANT TO HAVE ON
YOUR TRIBE.
AND COACH, HE IS JUST GOING TO
BE SO LOONY AND OUT THERE, HE'S
JUST GOING TO BE NUTS.
>> Jeff: THAT'S KIND A NICE
WELCOME.
>> IT'S THE BEST WELCOME EVER.
>> Jeff: IN A CUTTHROAT GAME.
>> OH, YEAH, DEFINITELY.
>> DEFINITELY.
>> Jeff: WOMAN IN THE FRONT.
>> CHRISTINE.
>> Jeff: CHRISTINE, REACTION
TO SEEING COACH AND OZZY COMING
BACK INTO THE GAME?
>> OZZY AND THE DRAGON WARRIOR
( LAUGHTER )
IT'S GOOD TO SEE THEM.
YOU KNOW.
IT'S NICE.
( LAUGHTER )
>> Jeff: MEANING?
>> THEY'RE TEMPORARY PLAYERS.
>> OOOH.
OUCH.
>> Jeff: GUY IN THE BACK,
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
>> JOHN.
I MEAN, OKAY, I KNOW THAT, LIKE,
THE PLAYERS YOU REALLY LIKE YOU
TEND TO CALL THEM BY THEIR LAST
NAMES.
I WAS HOPING YOU COULD CALL ME
COCHRAN AND CONTINUE THE
TRADITION OF DONALDSON, PEN EROB
MARIANOIANO, COCHRAN, I THINK I
FIT IN THAT LINEAGE PERFECTLY.
>> Jeff: ALL GREAT PLAYERS.
>> YEAH.
>> Jeff: WE'LL SEE IF YOU LIVE
UP, COCHRAN.
COCHRAN, REACTION TO SEEING
COACH AND OZZY.
>> I MEAN THEY HAVE SO MUCH
EXPERIENCE.
THIS IS THEIR THIRD TIME EACH.
THEY HAVE SO MUCH KNOWLEDGE OF
THE GAME AND IN TERMS OF THE
SURVIVING THAT I THINK THEY'LL
BE HUGE ASSETS TO US.
>> Jeff: COCHRAN YOU DIDN'T
EVEN HESITATE WHEN YOU SAID THEY
BOTH PLAYED TWO TIMES BEFORE.
YOU KNEW THAT.
>> YES.
I AM A FAN OF THE GAME.
SO I'M NOT GOING TO HIDE THAT.
I'M-- YOU KNOW, THIS IS AN
OUT-OF-BODY EXPERIENCE FOR ME
RIGHT NOW.
I HAVE A BUFF COLLECTION AT
HOME.
I CAN PLAY IT COOL BUT IT'S NOT
GOING TO WORK.
IT'S GOING TO BE TRANSPARENT SO
I'LL COME CLEAN AND SAY I'M A
HUGE FAN AND THRILLED TO SEE OZY
AND COACH.
>> Jeff: ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME
TO FIND OUT WHICH TRIBE COACH
AND OZZY ARE GOING TO BE ON.
THERE ARE TWO EGGS, ONE HAS BLUE
PAINT INSIDE, ONE HAS RED PAINT
INSIDE.
CHOOSE YOUR EGG.
>> OH, MAN.
>> Jeff: DON'T SMASH IT YET.
ALL RIGHT, THREE, TWO, ONE.
SMASH.
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> ON MY HEART.
>> I COULDN'T HAVE BEEN HAPPY
THEY'RE IT WAS OZO MY TRIBE.
OZZY!
FREAKING OZZY FROM "COOKS
ISLAND."
FANS VERSUS FAVORITES.
>> AS A HUGE FAN OF SURVIVOR
IT'S ACTUALLY A THRILL TO BE
PLAYING WITH SOMEBODY I WATCHED
AND TO SOME EXTENTIZEOLIDED.
>> Jeff: COACH JOINS THE BLUE
TRIBE.
>> I DID NOT WANT TO SEE COACH'S
EGG BLEED BLUE.
IT IT DID.
I HAVE NEVER, EVER SEEN THE
DRAGON SLAYER AND THERE AIN'T NO
DRAGONS.
HE'S IN HIS 40s.
GOD.
>> Jeff: HERE'S YOUR BAG AND
WATER BOTTLE.
SAY HELLO.
>> HELLO, GUYS HOW YOU DOING?
>> I'M NOT FEELING A GOOD VIBE
FROM THE BLUE TRIBE.
I SEE ONE LADY THAT'S SHOOTING
DAGGERS AT ME, THE ONE THAT SAID
WE'RE TEMPORARY PLAYERS.
SO RIGHT AWAY I'VE GOT, LIKE,
NEGATIVE VIBES.
SO NEGATIVE THAT I KIND OF
GRABBED A HOLD OF MY CHEEKS
RIGHT HERE AND THOUGHT HOLD ON
FOR THE RIDE BECAUSE IT'S GOING
TO BE ROCKY IN THE BEGINNING.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO HAVE
TWICE THE SLAYER CHARM TO GET
THROUGH THESE FIRST COUPLE OF
DAYS.
>> Jeff: OZZY, YOU JOAN THE
RED TRIBE AND SAY HELLO.
( APPLAUSE )
>> YA.
>> YES!
>> I FELT LIKE I WAS RECEIVED A
LOT MORE WARMLY THAN COACH AND I
WAS ACTUALLY HOPING TO GO WITH
THE RED TRIBE.
THEY LOOK LIKE A GOOD, STRONG
TRIBE.
>> Jeff: ONCE AGAIN,
REDEMPTION ISLAND IS IN PLAY.
THAT MEANS, WHEN YOU ARE VOTED
OUT OF YOUR TRIBE, YOU'RE NOT
OUT OF THE GAME.
YOU WILL BE SENT TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND WHERE YOU WILL LIVE
ALONE.
WHEN THE NEXT PERSON IS VOTED
OUT, THEY'LL JOIN YOU ON
REDEMPTION ISLAND, AND THE TWO
OF YOU WILL RETURN HERE TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND ARENA WHERE
YOU WILL SQUARE OFF IN A DUEL.
THE WINNER STAYS, THE LOSER IS
OUT FOR GOOD.
AT A CERTAIN POINT, THE PERSON
REMAINING ON REDEMPTION ISLAND
WILL RE-ENTER THE GAME AND
CONTINUE THEIR QUEST FOR THE
MILLION DOLLARS.
ALL RIGHT, IT IS TIME TO GET TO
OUR FIRST CHALLENGE.
>> WOW.
>> Jeff: IT IS A HERO
CHALLENGE.
OZZY IS GOING TO SQUARE UP
AGAINST COACH.
>> COACH, COME ON, NOW.
>> YOU GOT IT, YOU GOT IT!
>> RIGHT AWAY.
>> Jeff: THIS IS A CHANCE FOR
YOU GUYS TO PROVE YOUR WORTH.
HERE'S HOW IT GOES-- ON MY GO,
YOU WILL CLIMB TO THE TOP OF A
12-FOOT POLE WHERE YOU WILL
RETRIEVE A WOODEN TURTLE.
YOU WILL THEN CRAWL UNDER A LOG.
FINALLY YOU MUST TRANSFER YOUR
PYRAMID PUZZLE ACROSS A SERIES
OF TABLES TO THE THIRD TABLE.
MOVING ONLY ONE PIECE AT A TIME
AND ALWAYS MOVING SMALLER PIECES
ON TOP OF LARGER PIECES.
THE FIRST PERSON TO TRANSFER
THEIR PUZZLE TO THE THIRD TABLE
WITH THE TURTLE ON TOP WINS FOR
THEIR TRIBE REWARD.
THIS IS TERRA.
IT IS A STAPLE HERE IN THE SOUTH
PACIFIC.
IT'S THE EQUIVALENT OF POTATOES
FOR US BACK IN THE U.S.
ALONG WITH FIRE IN THE FORM OF
FLINT, A GIGANTIC ADVANTAGE
ADVANTAGE TO START THIS GAME OFF
WITH.
ARE YOU GUYS READY FOR THIS?
>> YES.
>> YOU GOT IT.
YOU GOT IT.
>> Jeff: TRIBES TAKE A SPOT.
COACH, OZZY, TAKE YOUR SPOTS FOR
THE CHALLENGE AND WE WILL GET
STARTED.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
OUR FIRST CHALLENGE OF THE
SEASON.
CHANCE FOR OZY AND COACH TO PUT
UP OR MAYBE SHUT UP.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO.
OZZY'S UP QUICKLY, HAS THE
TURTLE AND HE'S DOWN.
COACH HAS HISSY TURTLE.
HE'S DOWN.
( APPLAUSE )
BOTH GUYS NOW DIGYING.
>> DIG, DIG, DIG!
>> Jeff: BOTH HAVE PLAYED THIS
GAME TWICE BEFORE.
THEY SHOULD BOTH BE CALM.
>> COACH, COME ON NOW.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> YEAH, YEAH, YEAH!
OH, YEAH!
>> YOU GOT IT.
COME ON!
>> Jeff: COACH DIGGING A BIG
HOLE.
OZZY GOING FOR IT.
OZZY PULLING HIS BODY UNDERNEATH
THE POLE.
>> COME OCOACH!
GET IN N-GET IN!
>> LET'S GO, COACH!
>> Jeff: OZZY IS THROUGH.
COACH IS GOING TO GIVE IT A GO.
CAN HE MAKE IT?
>> COME ON, COACH!
PUSH!
>> Jeff: OZZY STARTING TO WORK
ON THE PUZZLE.
COACH IS THROUGH, HE'S WORKING
ON HIS PUZZLE.
ONE PIECE AT A TIME.
SMALLER PIECES ON TOP OF BIGGER
PIECES.
>> YEAH!
>> Jeff: ONE AT A TIME.
ONE PUZZLE PIECE AT A TIME!
MOVE IT BACK!
ONE AT A TIME.
NOTHING BIGGER ON SMALLER.
COACH, COACH.
YOU CAN'T GO BIG ON TOP OF
SMALL.
>> SMALL TO TOP OF BIG.
IT'S COMPLICATED.
WE GET IT.
ONE PIECE AT A TIME.
>> THERE YOU GO!
>> Jeff: SLOW DOWN AND JUST
START MOVING PIECES.
>> COME ON, OZZY!
>> Jeff: THIS IS A VERY
COMPLICATED PUZZLE.
>> HELP ME OUT.
>> RIGHT TO THE MIDDLE, TURTLE
TO THE TOP.
>> SAVAII HELPING OZZY.
THEY WANT THE FIRST WIN.
>> TURTLE ON THE BIG STARCH.
>> Jeff: UPOLO HELPING COACH.
>> Jeff: THIS IS HOW
"SURVIVOR" WORKS RIGHT HERE.
TEAM WORK!
>> GOOD JOB, MAN!
GOOD JOB.
>> Jeff: IT STARTED AS A HERO
DUEL.
IT IS NOW A TRIBE CHALLENGE.
>> FAR LEFT TO THE FAR RIGHT.
>> YES!
>> YOU GOT IT, YOU GOT IT!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
>> GOOZZY, GO.
>> Jeff: OZZY HAS THE BASE OF
HIS PUZZLE ON THE FINISH TABLE.
>> NO, NO, NO.
NO.
BACKWARDS.
>> BRING THAT OVER.
>> COACH WHY-- NO!
>> Jeff: UPOLO HAS BEEN GIVING
COACH A LOT OF HELP.
THUS FAR, IT IS NOT WORKING.
SAVAII, ON THE OTHER HAND,
GIVING OZZY A LOT OF HELP AND IT
APPEARS TO BE WORKING.
>> TURTLE RIGHT.
TURTLE MIDDLE.
RIGHT, LEFT.
( APPLAUSE )
>> GO, OZZY!
>> Jeff: OZZY IN THE LEAD
RIGHT NOW.
>> YES!
>> NO, NO, NOTICE.
>> THAT ONE OVER THERE.
>> NO, NO, STOP, STOP!
TURTLE OVER HERE, TURTLE TO ME.
>> WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
GO BACK, GO BACK.
RIGHT, LEFT.
>> OH, MY GOD, YOU'RE GOING TO
GET IT!
>> Jeff: OZZY VERY CLOSE.
OZZY WINS FOR SAVAII!
>> WE KNOT IT, OZZY!
>> THANK YOU, OZZY.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, BROTHER.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE
HERE.
>> GOOD JOB!
>> Jeff: OZZY, I FEEL LIKE I
NEEDED TO CONGRATULATE THE
ENTIRE TRIBE.
>> HEAL, HELL, YEAH, YOU DO.
>> Jeff: THAT WAS A TRIBE WIN.
>> THERE'S NO WAY I COULD HAVE
DONE IT WITHOUT THEM.
I MIGHT HAVE BUT WE WOULD BE
HERE ALL DAY.
>> Jeff: OZZY COME AND COLLECT
THE REWARD YOU EARNED FOR YOUR
TRIBE.
>> OH, IT'S HEAVY.
>> Jeff: YOU'VE GOT TAROT,
FLINT FOR FIRE AND A MAP TO YOUR
NEW HOME.
HEAD OUT, GUYS.
GOOD LUCK.
>> WE DON'T HAVE TO HEAR I GOT
NOTHING FOR YOU, HEAD BACK TO
CAMP.
>> I GOT NOTHING FOR YOU, GET
YOUR LAME ASSES OUT.
>> Jeff: UPOLO, ALL I'VE GOT
FOR YOU IS A MAP TO YOUR NEW
HOME.
HEAD ON OUT.
DOWN THE BEACH TO YOUR RIGHT.
>> NEED SOME HELP, COACH?
>> THANK YOU.
>> I LOST THE CHALLENGE.
MY TRIBE WALKS OFF AND ONE
PERSON STOPS AND HELPS ME.
WHAT WAS YOUR NAME?
>> I'M EDNA.
>> EDNA.
I LIKE YOUR SMILE.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS JUST LIKE
DON'T LET THE DOOR SMACK YOUR
ASS ON THE WAY OUT, ESSENTIALLY.
RIGHT OFF THE BAT I HAVE TO COME
FACE TO FACE WIT
>> YEAH!
>> YES!
( APPLAUSE )
>> WE GOT THE FIRE.
>> NICE JOB.
>> WE GOT THE FIRE
>>
>> I THINK IT'S REALLY ACTUALLY
KIND OF NICE TO HAVE PLAYED THIS
GAME A FEW TIMES AND KNOW WHAT'S
UP AHEAD OF YOU.
>> SO, OZZY, WE'RE LOOKING UP TO
YOU RIGHT NOW.
>> YEAH.
I THINK THAT A NEW TRIBE LIKE
THIS LOOKING AT ME AS A
RETURNING PLAYER,UN, THEY WANT
ME TO TELL THEM HOW TO DO
EVERYTHING.
YEAH, LET'S KEEP WALKING AROUND.
LET'S KEEP CHECKING IT.
I'M TRYING TO COME OUT HERE AND
I'M TRYING TO PLAY A STRATEGIC
GAME THIS TIME.
>> WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> I'M A LAW STUDENT.
>> WHY WHERE?
>> WHERE DO YOU GO?
>> HARVARD.
>> I'M A SONGWRITER, I LIVE IN
NASHVILLE.
>> MY TALENT, MY LIFE, IS
POETRY.
THE SPOKEN WORD.
>> SAY SOMETHING.
>> I WOULD WALK MILES AND MILES
TO PROTECT HIS AGELESS LIFE OF A
CHILD, ONLY STEPPING ON THE
WHITE ONES.
( APPLAUSE )
I GOT PUT ON THE SPOT.
SO I IMMEDIATELY HAD TO STEP UP.
I'M NOT OF NOT GOING TO SAY THAT
I'M A POTET AND THEN NOT HAVE
ANYTHING TO SHOW FOR IT.
SOIN IT'S IMPORTANT WHEN PEOPLE
CHALLENGE YOU THAT YOU STEP UP
TO THAT SO THAT THEY KNOW THAT
THEY CAN TRUST YOU AND THEY KNOW
YOUR WORD IS REAL.
>> SAY YOUR NAME ONE MORE TIME.
>> SEMHAR.
I THINK SEMHAR, SHE'S DEFINITELY
BEAUTIFUL TO LOOK AT.
WHEN SHE DID HER POEM, I THOUGHT
IT WAS BEAUTIFUL, AND I THINK
THAT SHE'S INCREDIBLY TALENTED.
>> I'VE BEEN DOING THAT SINCE I
WAS 15, PERFORMING THE SPOKEN
WORD.
>> I RESPECT SEMHAR'S PASSION
AND I THINK I WOULD LIKE TO HAVE
SOMEBODY LIKE HER ALONGSIDE ME
FOR THE LONG HAUL.
I'VE HAD A FEW TRIBES.
THIS IS THE BEST TRIBE, EVER.
>> YA!
>> REALLY, WE HAVE THE
ADVANTAGE.
WE REALLY DON'T DON'T HAVE TO
WORRY AND I DON'T THINK WE
SHOULD BREAK OUR NECKS TOO HARD.
I THINK WE SHOULD ENJOY THIS.
LET'S GO SWIMMING.
LET'S RELAX A LITTLE BIT.
>> SWIM BREAK!
>> COME ON, GUYS.
IT'S SO NICE.
>> YOU CAN DO IT.
>> YOU'RE DOING IT?
>>
>> YEAH, I DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
>> OZZY SUGGESTED LET'S JUST
KIND OF HAVE FUN IN THE OCEAN.
SO THE ONLY OPTION WAS TO GET
IN, IN OUR UNDERWEAR, AND I WAS
REALLY OPPOSED TO DOING THIS.
ARE YOU DOING THIS, KEITH?
YOU HAVE NOTHING TO BE ASHAMED
OF, THOUGH.
THAT'S THE THING.
YOU CAN WALTZ IN THERE IN YOUR
UNDERPANTS.
>> NEITHER DO YOU.
>> I HAVE TRANSLUCENT SKIN AND,
YOU KNOW-- I HAVE THIS REAL
PALE SKIN.
YOU CAN PRACTICALLY SEE THROUGH
IT.
YOU YOU CAN SEE MY ORGANS
BEATING THROUGH MY SKIN.
I WASN'T CRAZY ABOUT GOING IN
THE WATER.
IT IS JUST GOING TO MAKE ME LOOK
LIKE MORE OF A PATHETIC TWERP.
>> IT'S LIKE A BAND-AID.
RIP IT OFF.
>> YEAH
( LAUGHTER )
>> FAKE IT TILL YOU MAKE IT.
>> OH NO!
I LOOK DIFFERENT FROM EVERYBODY
ELSE ON MY TRIBE.
WE HAVE THIS BEVY OF BEAUTIFUL
BIKINI BABES, THESE YOUNG,
BEAUTIFUL WOMEN.
THIS IS WHAT IT'S COME TO.
IF THIS IS LIKE THE "900 2-1 0"
TRIBE I'M ONE OF THE ZEROES.
I HAVE TO FOCUS ON THE POSITIVE,
VISUALIZE SUCCESS.
>> COME ON!
( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )
( APPLAUSE )
>> LOOK AT HIM.
SLOW MOTION, SLOW MOTION.
( LAUGHTER )
>> WHEN I LOST THE CHALLENGE,
WHEN I GOT ON A TRIBE THAT WAS
SHOOTING DAGGERS AND GIVING ME
THE COLD SHOULDER, I WAS AFRAID.
I WAS AFRAID.
HOME, SWEET HOME.
>> HERE WE ARE.
>> AND SO I HAD TO COME FACE TO
FACE WITH THAT FEAR.
YOU KNOW, YOU CAN'T RUN AWAY
FROM FEAR.
YOU CAN'T RUN AWAY FROM
OBSTACLES.
SO I GUESS THE FIRST THING IS,
YOU KNOW, WE'VE GOT TO GET A
SHELTER BUILT.
BY THE WAY, I DON'T WANT YOU
GUYS TO LOOK AT ME LIKE I'M A
THREAT.
I'M NOT A STRATEGIC PLAYER.
I'M STRAIGHT AS AN ARROW.
THAT'S ALWAYS BEEN MY DOWNFALL.
I'M SORRY I LOST THE CHALLENGE
BUT WHAT I REALLY LIKED ABOUT IT
IS I FELT LIKE IT WAS A TEAM
EFFORT.
>> RIGHT.
>> DOES ANYBODY HAVE ANY
EXPERIENCE BUILDING-- MAYBE WE
CAN TALK ABOUT OUR OCCUPATIONS.
>> OKAY, HOW ABOUT YOU?
WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> I'M A RANCHER.
>> AWESOME.
>> I'M ACTUALLY A BASEBALL
COACH.
SO COACH AND I--
>> WHAT.
>> I JUST GRADUATED COLLEGE,
LIKE, FOUR DAYS AGO.
>> WITH WHAT DEGREE?
>> I WAS A RUSSIAN AND ECONOMICS
MAJOR.
>> COOL.
>> IS THAT IT?
>> I KNOW A LITTLE BIT MORE.
>> I'M A RUSSIAN ECONOMICS
MAJOR.
COACH-- SAYS A PRETTY FORMAL WAY
TO SAY HELLO.
WITH.
>> THE FIRST THING WE NEED TO DO
IS PICK A LOCATION.
>> YOU CAN'T DENY WHAT THE
SITUATION IS.
COACH HAS BEEN OUT HERE TWICE
BEFORE.
HE KNOWS SOME THINGS.
>> I LIKE THIS SPOT.
>> LOOK AT THAT.
YOU LADIES ARE AWESOME!
>> DOES GIRTH MATTER ON THESE,
COACH.
>> SOUNDS LIKE TWO SQUIRRELS
MAKING LOVE.
>> YOU MUST LIVE NEAR A LOT OF
SQUIRRELS.
>> I JUST SPEND A LOT OF TIME BY
MYSELF.
( LAUGHTER )
>> JUST KEEP PEELING IT APART
LIKE THIS.
AND THEN YOU JUST PULL IT OUT
LIKE THAT AND EAT IT.
IT'S REALLY SWEET.
>> IT'S CHEWY.
I LIKE COACH.
I THINK HE'S A TEAM PLAYER.
HE'S DEFINITELY WORKING WELL
WITH OTHERS.
AND HE'S SHOWING US THESE LITTLE
TINY TRICKS, LITTLE THINGS LIKE
THAT.
RIGHT NOW I THINK HE'S AN ASSET.
>> PRETTY EASY.
>> I'M GOING TO LOOK FOR
FIREWOOD.
I AM A BIG FAN OF "SURVIVOR," SO
I WOULD HAVE TO ASSUME THAT
THERE'S A HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL
SOMEWHERE.
BUT SO FAR, NOTHING.
I DON'T THINK I NEED IT.
BUT IT'S NICE TO HAVE IT IN YOUR
BACK POCKET.
SHOOT.
WHERE ARE YOU?
>> SHE'S LOOK FOR THE IDOL, MAN,
100%.
>> CHRISTINE SCARES ME THE MOST.
SHE SAID RIGHT OFF THE BAT, "YOU
ARE A TEMPORARY PLAYER."
AND THEN SHE GOES LOOKING FOR
THE IMMUNITY IDOL LIKE CRAZY.
I MEAN, LOOK, WHEN I GOT ON TO
THIS BEACH I WASN'T THINKING
ABOUT AN IMMUNITY IDOL.
I WAS THINKING ABOUT PUTTING A
SHELTER TOGETHER AND MAKING THIS
AS LIVABLE AS POSSIBLE.
SO NO QUESTION ABOUT IT,
CHRISTINE IS TARGET NUMBER ONE.
>> I'M NOT VERY SHY, SO--
UNFORTUNATELY FOR Y'ALL.
OZZY GAVE THE IDEA OF GOING TO
HAVE A DIP.
IT WAS THE FIRST TIME WE'D HAD
SEEN THIS BEAUTIFUL, BEAUTIFUL
PLACE THAT WE'RE IN.
AND I WAS SO EXCITED.
WE'VE TO THE THREE GIRLS ON OUR
TRIBE THAT ARE HOT AS HELL.
BOOM!
LOVED IT.
>> WHAT DO YOU DO AGAIN?
>> TEACHER.
>> WHAT DO YOU TEACH?
>> SCIENCE.
ACTUALLY, I TEACH FORENSIC
SCIENCE.
>> OH!
>> I'M THE COOL HIGH SCHOOL
TEACHER, MR. COTTER.
I'M NOT A TEACHER.
I HAVE AN MBA.
I'VE WON OVER 20 POKER
TOURNAMENTS AND I OWN TWO
MEDICAL MARIJUANA DISPENSARIES.
BUT I'M NOT GOING TO TELL ANY OF
THEM THAT.
WHY WOULD I.
>> WHO IS MARRIED?
>> GOOD CALL.
>> I HAVE A BOYFRIEND.
>> I'VE BEEN GAY ALL MY LIFE--
MOST OF MY LIFE.
>> I WOULD NOT HAVE GUESSED.
>> PLEASE, THERE ARE FEATHERS
FLYING AROUND ME
( LAUGHTER )
YOU KNOW, I'M HERE FOR THE
MILLION DOLLARS JUST LIKE
EVERYBODY ELSE BUT I'M ALSO HERE
FOR ANOTHER REASON-- I'M OLDER
THAN MOST OF THOSE OTHER GUYS,
AND I'M EXPERIENCING LIFE FREE
OF EVERYTHING THAT WOULD
RESTRICT ME.
I CAME OUT OF THE JOB BECAUSE I
FELT, YOU KNOW, IF IT COULD
OTHER COPS BEHIND ME.
>> RIGHT.
>> IT WOULD HELP THEM.
BEING GAY, IT'S WHO I AM.
IF THEY DON'T LIKE IT... I THINK
I LOOK LIKE A BEAR, WHAT DO YOU
THINK?
>> A BEAR.
>> I'VE BEEN CALLED DADDY BEAR.
I'M A BEAR, DEFINITELY A BEAR.
I'M PAPA BEAR FROM NOW ON.
IT'S NOT ABOUT BEING GAY.
IT'S ABOUT SURVIVING.
I'M A GUY WHO SIA TEAM PLAYER
AND HOPEFULLY THEY'LL SEE THAT
AND KEEP ME.
>> WE NEED TO GET FIRE GOING.
FIRE TO MAKE SURE WE HAVE EXTRA
WATER.
>> IT FEELS LIKE THE TRIBE IS
REALLY SPENDING THIS TIME KIND
OF FORMING A BOND BUT COMING
INTO TODAY, I HAD THESE HOPES
THAT, YOU KNOW, WE'D BE REALLY
ORGANIZED, ESPECIALLY AFTER
WINNING AND GETTING THE FLINT
AND THE FOOD.
SO IN MY MIND THIS DAY WAS GOG
END WITH KIND OF THE SHELTER
DONE.
>> I FEEL LIKE EVERY TIME I
WATCH AND THEY DON'T HAVE THE
SHELTER ON DAY ONE, IT WORRIES
ME.
>> WELL--
>> IT'S OKAY.
WE'RE GOING TO GET THROUGH THIS.
>> WE'LL BE FINE.
>> I'M GOING TO TRY TO GET
THROUGH THIS.
IT PROBABLY TAKES A WHILE TO
RELAX AND LET THINGS HAPPEN.
I HAVE SIX KIDS.
I'M USED TO BEING IN CHARGE.
>> HONESTLY, IF IT DOESN'T RAIN
TONIGHT I'M SO HAPPY SLEEPING ON
THE GROUND.
>> IT SEEMS LIKE WE SHOULD HAVE
KIND OF A LEADER, AND FOR ME,
OZZY, HE'S A LITTLE BOB MARLEY
TO ME.
YOU KNOW, I'M A PLANNER.
AND I'M NOT SURE BOB MARLEY IS.
>> SO FAR, SO GOOD.
>> BY THE WAY, WHAT'S THIS RIGHT
HERE?
>> LOCO, MAN.
>> YOU MEAN, BECAUSE YOU'RE A
BULL RIDER.
>> I FIRST TIME I SAW IT I
THOUGHT IT SAID "LOVE."
AND I WAS LIKE IT SAYS LOCO.
I WAS LIKE THAT'S BAD ASS.
>> I'M ASHAMED OF THAT TATTOO,
MAN.
I HAVE A TATTOO ON MY HEAD THAT
SAYS LOCO.
IN SPANISH THAT MEANS CRAZY.
SO RIGHT OFF THE BAT, PEOPLE ARE
GOING TO START LOOKING AT MY
NECK AND THINKING I'M REALLY
CRAZY.
AT ONE POINT IN MY LIFE I KIND
OF WAS CRAZY BUT IT WAS A
CHILDISH THING DI.
I TRIED TO ACT LIKE RUSSELL IN
HIGH SCHOOL.
I WAS BULLYING EVERYBODY.
AND I'M REALLY NOT LIKE THAT.
I'M A DIFFERENT PERSON NOW.
I GREW UP A LOT.
GOD IS NUMBER ONE FOR ME.
>> MIKAYLA'S A PRETTY GOOD
MORNING.
>> I DON'T KNOW, MAN.
I THINK SHE'S GONNA ASK A LOT.
>> ARE YOU UP?
>> YUP.
>> BE CAREFUL UP THERE.
>> I'M GOOD.
>> WE'RE DOING THE SHELTER, AND
WE NEEDED TO GET THE TOP DONE.
>> CAN SOMEBODY HAND ME ONE SO I
CAN START DOING THIS AREA?
ME AND MY BROTHERS USED TO CLIMB
TREES WHEN WE WERE YOUNGER SO I
GOT RIGHT UP THERE AND WAS JUST
GETTING TO IT, AND WHEN THE TIME
COMES WE HAVE TO GET DOWN AND
DIRTY.
THIS IS A GAME, LIKE, YOU
COULDN'T BE A LITTLE PRINCESS.
I HAVE TWO COMING UP TOP RIGHT
HERE.
I DON'T HAVE PATIENCE.
I JUST WANT TO GET STUFF DONE SO
I HAD NO PROBLEM HOPPING UP
THERE AND GETTING MY HANDS
DIRTY.
YOU GOT SOME MORE OF THAT STUFF
AND WE'LL DO THIS LITTLE CORNER
RIGHT HERE?
>> I DON'T FEEL COMFORTABLE
AROUND MIKAYLA.
IT'S JUST THE WAY THAT SHE
CARRIES HERSELF.
THE WAY THAT SHE FLAUNT HERSELF
OFF.
>> YOU WANT A BIG ONE?
>> YEAH, GIVE ME WHAT YOU GOT.
>> YOU KNOW, I GREW UP IN THE
CHURCH, AND I STRAYED OFF FOR A
LITTLE BIT, AND I'VE COME BACK
TO, YOU KNOW, FIND GOD AGAIN AND
HE'S ALWAYS BEEN THERE FOR ME IN
TOUGH TIMES, ME BEING A YOUNG
MARRIED GENTLEMAN.
I'M NOT GOING TO DRAW CLOSE TO A
SITUATION THAT I KNOW I CAN GET
MYSELF IN TROUBLE IN.
IT'S-- IT'S NOT COOL FOR
>> LOOK AT THESE STARS.
THEY'RE ALREADY OUT.
YOU TONIGHT SEE THIS IN TEXAS,
MAN.
>> I WISH WE HAD AN ASTROLOGER
HERE TO TELL US STORIES.
I'M SURE COACH COULD DO IT,
BUT...
( LAUGHTER ).
>> THE DRAGON SLAYER!
YEAH!
>> THERE WAS FIVE OF US SITTING
OUT BY THEICA ME.
IT WAS JUST KIND OF LIKE A
FEEL-OUT SESSION, GET TO KNOW
EVERYBODY.
WE WERE TALKING ABOUT EVERYTHING
UNDER THE SUN FOR A LONG TIME.
I WOULD LOVE TO GO AND WIN EVERY
IMMUNITY.
>> THAT'S GOAL.
>> THE CHALLENGES-- IT'S GREAT
TO WIN REWARD CHALLENGES.
IT KEEPS YOUR STRENGTH UP AND
ALL THAT KIND OF STUFF, BUT
WINNING IMMUNITY, MAN, THAT'S
THE BEST THING.
THAT'S THE BEST THING TO DO.
IF YOU HAVE A STRONG FIVE, YOU
CAN GO-- YOU CAN GO SO FAR, EVEN
YOU'RE DOWN NUMBERS AT THE
MERGE.
I GUARANTEE YOU, IF YOU HAVE A
STRONG FIVE THAT HAVE GOOD VIBES
WITH EACH OTHER, TRUST EACH
OTHER, THAT'S AN ALMOST
IMPOSSIBLE NUT TO CRACK IN THIS
GAME.
THERE'S NOT GOING TO BE ANOTHER
CHANCE IN THIS GAME WHERE THE
FIVE OF US CAN SIT DOWN AND TALK
AND THAT'S I DIDN'T POUNCED ON
IT TO TALK ABOUT HOW WE CAN GO
AND PLAY THIS GAME TOGETHER.
>> I'M GOING TO TELL YOU RIGHT
NOW, THE FOUR PEOPLE SITTING
RIGHT HERE WITH ME ARE THE FOUR
PEOPLE I'VE GOTTEN THE BEST VIBE
FROM BAR NONE.
>> I'M WITH HIM, BROTHER.
>> I AGREE WITH HIM COMPLETELY.
>> I AGREE.
>> FIRST-DAY ALLIANCES ARE THE
MOST SOLID.
YOU'VE SEEN IT TIME AND TIME
AGAIN.
NOW WE'VE GOT A PEACE OF MIND,
JUST GO OUT THERE AND HAVE FUN.
I THINK I'M SITTING PRETTY.
AND I SURE AS HELL WASN'T AT THE
CHALLENGE.
I WAS IN A BIND.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE THE DIFFERENCE
A DAY MAKES.
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING, COACH
IS HERE TO PLAY THE GAME THIS
TIME, OKAY.
I'M NOT GOING TO DO ANYTHING
SNEAKY OR DISHONORABLE BUT THIS
IS COACH 3.0, I'M HERE TO WIN.
>> I'LL MOVE IT.
READY?
I GOT IT WITH MY HAND.
>> OKAY, THAT'S PERFECT.
>> AAH!
>> FOR REAL?
>> NO!
>> ALL RIGHT, WHATEVER.
LET'S DO THIS AGAIN.
>> I WANT MY MOMMY.
I THINK SO DAY TWO FOR ME IS
STARTING OFF A LITTLE ROCKY.
I REALLY DIDN'T SLEEP SO I THINK
I MIGHT BE HAVING A MINI-
MINI-BREAKDOWN.
I'M GOING TO BE OKAY ABOUT THE
I'M FEELING IT.
BEING DOWN ON THE WATER IS
OVERWHELMING FOR ME.
I'M USED TO DRINKING SO MUCH
WATER MY CALVES ARE COMPLETELY
CRAMPED.
>> YOU HAVE TO BE STRONG.
THEY'RE GOING TO TURNOUS, TOO.
REMEMBER WE'RE THE OLDEST
PEOPLE.
THEY'RE YOUNG AND VIBRANT,
THEY'RE GOING TO STICK TOGETHER.
THAT'S HOW I FEEL.
>> RIGHT.
PAPA BEAR IS SAYING WE'RE THE
OLDEST ONES AND THAT MIGHT BE
PART OF IT, TOO, BECAUSE I FEEL
OLD FOR THE FIRST TIME IN
FOREVER.
I HAVEN'T FELT THAT WAY EVER.
AND I GUESS WE NEED VINES,
RIGHT, BECAUSE WE'RE GOING TO
THRASH.
I'M GOOD.
DON'T WORRY.
I REALLY AM OKAY.
I DON'T KNOW IF I AM.
I THINK I KIND OF WOKE UP TODAY
WITHOUT REALLY BEING ABLE TO
CONTAIN, LIKE, MY EMOTIONS.
AND IT REALLY IS OVERWHELMING.
I CAN TOTALLY GET WHY YOU ARE,
WHOA, I'M SPENT.
I CAN'T SEE WHERE THIS IS GOING
TO GO.
I DON'T CRACK, SO THIS IS
KILLING ME.
>> I KNOW.
>> OH, REALLY?
>> NO.
>> I'M GOOD.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
>> NO, BECAUSE THIS IS THE PART
WHERE I NEED, LIKE, HUMAN--
>> YES, OF COURSE.
THIS IS NOT-- THIS HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH THE GAME RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS TWO PEOPLE TALKING.
>> UH-HUH.
SERIOUSLY, THE PERSON THAT HAAS
THE BREAKDOWN GOES.
>> SHE WAS CRYING THIS MORNING
AND THAT SCARES THE CRAP OUT OF
ME BECAUSE DAWN AND I ARE, LET'S
FACE IT, WE'RE OLDER THAN MOST
PEOPLE OUT THERE.
WHEN YOU CRY FOR ANYTHING,
CRYING IS VIEWED AS A WEAKNESS.
BUT I'LL SUPPORT HER.
I WON'T TURN MY BACK ON HER,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
BECAUSE EVERYBODY HAS EMOTIONS.
>> JUST LOOK AT ME.
>> I'M, LIKE, 15 YEARS OLDER
THAN ALL OF YOU.
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER.
>> LIKE, I'M LIKE, WHERE IS MY
COMMON GROUND?
>>
>> UH-HUH.
>> SERIOUSLY, I HAVE IT
EVERYWHERE I GO, BUT I DON'T
HAVE IT HERE.
>> AS LONG AS YOU DON'T QUIT, AS
LONG AS YOU STAY STRONG AND
FIGHTING, YOU'LL BE IN THIS
GAME.
YOU HAVE WHAT IT TAKES TO KEEP
GOING BUT YOU HAVE SOMETHING
INSIDE OF YOU THAT'S UNSURE AND
YOU NEED TO-- YOU NEED TO
CONFRONT THAT AND TELL IT TO GET
THE HELL OUT.
I HAD A CONVERSATION WITH DAWN,
AND SHE'S A LITTLE SCATTER, A
LITTLE BIT FRAZZLED, A LITTLE
BIT-- VERY PARANOID, AND
WHATEVER I CAN DO TO CALM HER
NERVES IS MY JOB AT THIS POINT.
POINT.
IM THE ANCHOR.
LISTEN, I'M HERE FOR YOU.
IF YOU WANT ANY ADVICE, JUST ASK
ME.
>> IT SEEMS TOO WEAK.
I HATE IT.
I'M IN A MELT-DOWN.
>> I KNOW, I KNOW.
YOU DON'T NEED TO LET IT GET TO
YOU.
>> OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
>> JUST FEEL IT AND LET IT GO.
IT'S THE NAME OF THE GAME.
>> ALL RIGHT, THANKS FOR THE
TIME.
REALLY, I'M SORRY.
>> DON'T, DON'T BE SORRY.
I'M GOING TO GO AND TRY TO CATCH
US SOME FISH.
>> OKAY.
>> IF SHE CAN GET OUT OF HER
HEAD AND START TO TRUST ME SHE
MIGHT BE A VERY, VERY CRUCIAL
AND IMPORTANT ALLY.
BUT IF DAWN DOESN'T GET IT
TOGETHER SHE VERY
TOOTHPASTE, YOU CAN TAKE JUST
SOME ASH, AND YOU PUT JUST A
LITTLE BIT OF NATURE IT SO IT'S
PASTY, AND YOU CAN USE THAT AS
TOOTHPASTE.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF I'LL TAKE THE
PLUNGE AND USE THE
ASH TOOTHPASTE, BUT I'LL GO WITH
THE TOOTHBRUSH.
>> THIS MORNING, I'M DEFINITELY
STARTING TO FEEL LIKE WE NEED TO
START GETTING THINGS TOGETHER.
I KNOW FOR MY OWN SAKE THAT I'M
GOING TO BE OKAY BUT FOR
EVERYBODY ELSE, THE ELEMENTS,
THE STRESS, THE NOT EATING, THE
DAILY LABOR OF CAMP LIFE, IT'S
GOING TO START WEARING ON PEOPLE
AND IT ALREADY HAS.
BUT RIGHT NOW, WE'VE REALLY JUST
GOT TO KEEP A STRONG TRIBE.
THAT'S JUST "SURVIVOR TEN.1."
YOU'RE GETTING INTO THAT
COCONUT.
>> OH, MAN, I HAVE TO TRY THAT
NEXT.
>> YEAH, COCHRAN.
>> GIVE ME ADVICE.
TELL MAY WHO I'M DOING RIGHT AND
WRONG.
>> TAKE YOUR HAND BACK.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF I WILL GET
THE RIGHT SPOT.
>> I THINK I HEAR IT.
>> AN ALMOST MISHAP.
>> I'M A LITTLE SKEPTICAL OF
MR. COCHRAN.
HE DOESN'T SEEM LIKE HE HAS THE
MOST TO OFFER ON THE PHYSICAL
SIDE OF THINGS.
>> YOU SEE IT?
>> I SEE WHITE STUFF.
>> WHOO-HOO!
>> OH, MY GOD.
TRULY A COMING OF AGE STORY.
I TRY TO BE A PROVIDER.
THAT'S MY REAL PURPOSE IN LIFE.
I'M NOT THE STRONGEST GUY BUT I
THINK I HAVE ENOUGH SOCIAL GAME
TO KIND OF OVERCOME ANY DEFICITS
I HAVE.
>> COCKTAIL TIME.
>> PEOPLE SEEM TO LIKE ME A LOT.
IS CHARM AND SOME HUMOR ENOUGH
TO REALLY WANT TO KEEP SOMEBODY
AROUND?
I HOPE IT IS.
I ACCOMPLISHED WHAT I THOUGHT
WOULD BE IMPOSSIBLE, WHAT MY MOM
FORBADE ME FROM DOING.
>> I THINK MY UNCLE RUSSELL
LACKED IN THE SOCIAL GAME
DEFINITELY, BUT I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT, I WANT TO DO WHAT MY UNCLE
NEVER DID.
I'M TRYING TO PROVIDE FOOD FOR
MY TRIBE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S JUST GOING TO BE
TO MY ADVANTAGE.
HEY, GUYS!
>> YEAH.
>> FIRST FISH.
>> WHOOO!
>> FISH?
OH, MY GOD.
THAT GUY'S NOT WASTING ANY TIME.
>> I NEED SOMETHING TO HOLD HIM
IN.
EVEN THOUGH WE HAVE OUR ALLIANCE
OF FIVE I WILL NEVER REVEAL THAT
I'M RUSSELL HANTZ A NEPHEW.
AS LONG AS I KEEP MY SHIRT ON,
AS LONG AS I MAKE UP AN EXCUSE
WHY I WON'T TAKE IT OFF, I'VE
SHOWED THEM SOME TATTOO BUT I'LL
DEFINITELY NEVER SHOW THEM THIS
ONE OR THIS ONE.
>> HOW BIG?
>> I DON'T WANT TO BE JUDGED BY
MY UNCLE'S REPITATION.
>> I THINK I HAVE A REALLY GREAT
ADVANTAGE RIGHT NOW BECAUSE I
HAVE A STRONG ALLIANCE WHERE I
REALLY THINK, AT LEAST A COUPLE
OF PEOPLE THERE, ARE REALLY,
REALLY SINCERE.
BRANDON I'M A LITTLE MORE
WORRIED ABOUT ONLY BECAUSE I
HAVE THIS GUT FEELING-- I FEEL
LIKE HE'S HIDING SOMETHING.
>> Jeff: COME ON IN, GUYS!
YOU GUYS READY TO GET TO YOUR
FIRST IMMUNITY CHALLENGE?
>> YES.
>> YES, WE ARE.
>> Jeff: ON MY GO, BOTH TRIBES
WILL RACE THROUGH ZIGZAGGING
PATH WAYS AND THEN THROUGH A WEB
OF COCONUTS.
YOU MUST THEN WORK TOGETHER TO
GET ALL YOUR TRIBE MEMBERS OVER
A 10-FOOT WALL.
ONE TRIBE MEMBER WILL THEN DIG
UP A MASETY AND USE IT TO CHOP A
SERIES OF ROPES, RELEASING BANE
OF COCONUTS.
THREE TRIBE MEMBERS WILL THEN
SHOOT COCONUTS INTO YOUR BASKET.
FIRST TRIBE TO GET ENOUGH
COCONUTS IN THEIR BASKET TO
RAISE YOUR TRIBE FLAG WINS
IMMUNITY.
THIS IS WHAT THE GAME IS ALL
ABOUT
( APPLAUSE )
AS LONG AS YOU HAVE IMMUNITY,
YOU ARE SAFE FROM TRIBAL
COUNCIL.
YOU CAN'T BE VOTED OUT.
WINNERS ARE SAFE TONIGHT.
LOSERS GO TO TRIBAL COUNCIL
WHERE SOMEBODY WILL BE THE FIRST
PERSON VOTED OUT OF THIS GAME
AND SENT TO REDEMPTION ISLAND.
IN ADDITION, THE WINNING TRIBE
WILL WIN ONE CLUE TO THE
LOCATION OF A HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL WHICH I WILL TELL YOU AFTER
THE CHALLENGE.
ALSO, UPOLO, SINCE YOU DO NOT
HAVE FIRE, YOU ARE PLAYING FOR
FIRE IN THE FORM OF FLINT.
EVERYBODY READY FOR THIS?
>> YES!
>> Jeff: GIVE YOU A MINUTE TO
STRATEGIZE.
>> GOING UP OVER THE WALL.
WE NEED TO HAVE TWO PEOPLE
HOISTING ONE OVER TO GRAB TWO
PEOPLE, BOOM, BOOM, BOOM.
>> I'M COMFORTABLE SHOOTING--
>> I'M COMFORTABLE SHOOTING BUT
IF SOMEBODY IS REALLY, REALLY
GOOD, GO AHEAD.
BUT I'M GOOD.
>> I'LL BE ONE OF THOSE FOR
SURE.
>> I CAN AIM AND I CAN SHOOT.
THAT BASKET IS SO BIG.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> Jeff: HERE WE GO.
FOR IMMUNITY.
SURVIVORS READY?
GO!
BOTH TRIBES GETTING THROUGH THE
FIRST PART OF THIS FAIRLY
QUICKLY.
A LITTLE BIT OF MIXING IT UP.
EVERYBODY'S GOT TO GET TO THE
MAT BEFORE YOU CAN START THROUGH
THE COCONUTS.
>> ON THE GROUND, ON THE GROUND.
>> Jeff: COACH LEADING UPOLO
THROUGH THE COCONUTS.
GO, UPOLO!
UPOLO HITS THE WALL FIRST.
>> GET UP THERE, BUBBA.
COME ON!
>> HERE, HERE.
>> Jeff: RICK IS UP FIRST FOR
UPOLO.
ALBERT'S UP.
SAVAII, YOU'VE GOT SOME CATCHING
UP TO DO.
WHITNEY IS UP FIRST, GETTING A
HAND FROM KEITH AND JIM.
RICK PULLING UP EDNA.
EVERYBODY'S GOT TO GET OVER.
>> WHAT AM I DOING?
>> GET UP.
STAND ON US.
>> Reporter: UPOLO DOING A
GREAT JOB.
THEY'VE GOT A GREAT SYSTEM
GOING.
COCHRAN STRUGGLING TO GET OVER
THE WALL.
COACH IS OVER.
NOW BRANDON'S ON HIS OWN.
ALBERT PULLING BRANDON UP.
>> GOOD JOB, GUYS.
>> LET'S GO!
>> PULL ME UP.
>> YOU GOT IT!
>> YOU GOT IT, RICKY.
>> Jeff: RICK IS DIGGING,
LOOKING FOR THAT MACHETE.
OZZY PUSHING JIM OVER.
OZZY'S GOING TO GO IT ALONE.
OZZY, HE'S OVER.
EVERYBODY ON THE MAT.
GO!
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: OZZY'S GOT SOME TIME
TO MAKE UP NOW.
>> COME ON, YOU GUYS, RALLY.
>> LOOK AT THE SIDES, TOO, DON'T
FORGET THE SIDES.
>> COME ORICK!
>> Jeff: RICK'S GOT A HAND ON
IT.
>> LET'S GO, RICK!
>> Jeff: OZZY'S GOT HIS
MACHETE.
WE ARE NECK AND NECK IN OUR
FIRST IMMUNITY CHALLENGE.
>> COME OOZZY.
>> FIVE ROPES TO GET THROUGH.
RICK MAKING SHORT WORK OF THIS.
>> WHOOO!
>> Jeff: UPOLO RELEASES THEIR
COCONUTS.
GO.
OZZY VERY CLOSE.
>> SHOOT IT, GO!
>> TAKE YOUR TIME.
>> YOU WENT THROUGH THIS LIKE
BUTTER.
>> Jeff: OZZY RELEASES HIS
COCONUTS.
>> THREE MEMBERS OF EACH TRIBE.
SHOOTING COCONUTS.
>> COME ON, KEEP GOING.
WE GOT THIS!
>> OZZY SCORES.
SEMHAR SCORES.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET ENOUGH
COCONUTS TO LIFT YOUR BAG AND
RAISE YOUR FLAG.
>> COME OKEITH.
>> COME ON, COME ON!
>> Jeff: KEITH SCORES FOR
SAVAII.
UPOLO GETS THREE IN A ROW.
EVERY SHOT IS GOING TO COUNT.
WE ARE NOW NECK AND NECK.
SERVICEMEN SEMHAR JUST SHORT.
OZZY SCORES FOR SAVAII.
UPOLO DRILLS TWO WITH ALEXPERT
MIKAYLA.
>> YOU CAN DO IT.
ONE AT A TIME.
>> Jeff: KEITH SCORES FOR
SAVAII.
MIKAYLA IS A SCORING MACHINE.
>> TAKE YOUR TIME.
>> Jeff: SEMHAR, WAY SHORT.
>> ALL YOU GOT, ALL YOU GOT,
SEM.
>> CAN WE SWITCH OUT?
>> Jeff: NO, NO SWITCHING.
>> I'M SO TIRED.
>> COME ON, COME ON, COME ON.
>> Jeff: BRANDON MISSES.
OZZY SCORES.
ELBART COMES UP SHORT.
>> MORE OOMPH ON IT.
>> Jeff: KEITH HAS ANOTHER
SCORE.
THAT BAG IS STARTING TO LIST FOR
SAVAII.
IT'S STARTING TO LIFT FOR UPOLO.
>> COME ON!
>> Jeff: LET'S GO!
YOU'RE NECK AND NECK!
OZZY SCORES FOR SAVAII.
BRANDON SCORES AGAIN.
MIKAYLA KNOCKS ANOTHER ONE IN.
>> JUST A FEW MORE.
>> IT'S MOVING, KEITH.
>> Jeff: KEITH DRILLS ONE FOR
SAVAII.
MIKAYLA, THAT MIGHT DO IT.
UPOLO WINS IMMUNITY!
>> UPOLO!
UPOLO!
>> Jeff: THIS IS HOW CLOSE
THIS CHALLENGE WAS.
ONE COCONUT AWAY FROM SAVAII.
>> SORRY, GUYS.
>> WE'LL GET THEM NEXT TIME.
>> Jeff: ONE OF THE CLOSEST
CHALLENGES I'VE EVER SEEN IN
THIS GAME.
TRULY A GREAT FIRST EVER BY BOTH
TRIBES.
ONLY ONE TRIBE COMES UP WITH THE
WIN.
IMMUNITY FOR UPOLO.
>> GIVE US SOME LOVE.
GIVE US SOME LOVE.
>> Jeff: IN ADDITION YOU ALSO
WIN FIRE IN THE FORM OF FLINT.
ONE MORE THING FOR UPOLO.
HIDDEN BACK AT YOUR CAMP IS A
CLUE TO THE HIDDEN IMMUNITY
IDOL.
SO YOU HAVE TO FIRST FIND THE
CLUE, THEN USE THE CLUE TO HELP
YOU FIND THE HIDDEN IDOL.
MAKE SENSE?
>> UH-HUH.
>> Jeff: GRAB YOUR STUFF.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
CONGRATULATIONS.
SEMHAR, HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
ARE YOU EXHAUSTED, DEPRESSED?
>> I JUST FELT REALLY BAD
BECAUSE I WAS SO EXHAUSTED BY
THE TIME I GOT OVER AND DIDN'T
THINK THE COCONUTS WOULD BE THAT
HEAVY TO GET THROUGH, SO, YEAH,
I FEEL SORT OF BAD.
>> Jeff: JIM, IT'S LIKE YOU'RE
DOING MIME BACK THERE WITH YOUR
FACIAL EXPRESSIONS.
>> SORT OF BAD?
I FEEL LIKE EYE FEEL WORSE THAN
SORT OF BAD.
I FEEL SORT OF BAD WHEN I'M OUT
OF MILK.
>> I TRIED MY HARDEST.
>> I FEEL CRAP THAT WE'RE GOING
HOME TO VOTE SOMEBODY OUT.
>> Jeff: TONIGHT, TRIBAL
COUNCIL, WHERE SOMEBODY FROM
YOUR TRIBE WILL BE THE FIRST
PERSON VOTED OUT OF "SURVIVOR:
SOUTH PACIFIC" AND THE FIRST
PERSON SENT TO REDEMPTION
ISLAND.
YOU HAVE THE AFTERNOON TO FIGURE
OUT WHO IT IS GOING TO BE.
I WILL SEE YOU TONIGHT AT
TRIBAL.
GRAB YOUR STUFF AND HEAD BACK.
>> I'M PISSED THAT WE LOST.
SHE DOES TWO BASKETETS AND SHE
WANT A
>> HELL OF A JOB.
YOU GUYS ARE THRIVING.
THERE ARE TWO THINGS PEOPLE DO
IN THE WILD, THEY DIE OR THEY
THRIVE.
>> I WE WON THE CHALLENGE TODAY
BUT I THINK UNDERNEATH THIS
CELEBRATORY TONE THERE IS AN
UNEASINESS BECAUSE JEFF
MENTIONED THAT THE IMMUNITY IDOL
CLUE HIDDEN AT CAMP, PEOPLE NOW
KNOW THAT THE GAME HAS STARTED,
AND IT MIGHT JUST GET RUTHLESS.
>> LET'S JUST LOOK.
WE GOT TO LOOK, TOO.
>> HELL, YES.
>> THAT HIDDEN IMMUNITY IDOL IS
HERE SOMEWHERE.
IT'S A LOT OF SOMEWHERE IT COULD
BE.
>> LOOKING LIKE I'M LOOKING AND
WORKING AT THE SAME TIME.
TURNING OVER ROCK, LOOKING UP
HIGH, IN BIG TREES, LOOKING IN
THE HOLES OF THE TREES.
I'VE BEEN LOOKING.
PROBABLY BEING RIGHT IN OUR FACE
AND WE DON'T EVEN KNOW IT.
I PROBABLY COULD HAVE ALREADY
STUMBLED OVER IT AND DON'T EVEN
KNOW IT.
I PROBABLY HAVE ALREADY.
COULD PROBABLY BE RIGHT THERE.
>> I KIND OF HAVE SOMETHING TO
SAY.
I FELT AWFUL THAT WE LOST THAT
CHALLENGE, AND I KNOW THAT I WAS
A BIG PART OF THAT LAST PORTION,
BUT FOR SOMEONE, YOU,
PERSONALLY, WHO YOU MADE US LOOK
WEAK, AND I FEEL LIKE-- YEAH,
AND YOU CAN KEEP MAKING FACES
BUT IT DOESN'T MAKE ME TRUST
SOMEBODY WHEN THEY'RE MAKING
FACES BEHIND MY BACK WHEN I
ALREADY FEEL SO AWFUL.
>> FELT WORSE THAN YOU DID, I'M
SORRY--
>> YOU DIDN'T FEEL WORSE.
NO ONE CAN FEEL WORSE THAN I DO
RIGHT NOW.
I FEEL TERRIBLE.
LIKE, WHEN SOMEBODY IS ALREADY
DOWN, WHY PUSH THEM DOWN EVEN
MORE?
THAT'S ALL THAT I'M SAYING.
I REALLY TRIED TO BE POSITIVE
FOR US, AND I DO, I FEEL
TERRIBLE.
YOU WERE MAKING FACES BEHIND MY
BACK, AND THEN YOU SAY--
>> ACTUALLY, YOU DIDN'T SEE ANY
OF THAT.
>> I DID.
JEFF CALLED IT OUT.
>> HE SAID I WAS MIMING, WHEN
YOU SAID YOU FEEL SORT OF BAD I
ROLLED MY EYES.
I DID.
>> ALL I'M SAYING IS TRY NOT TO
JUST HURRY UP AND TURN ON
SOMEONE.
>> I APOLOGIZE IF THAT'S HOW IT
CAME ACROSS.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO BE TURNING ON
YOU.
EVERYBODY GAVE 100%.
THEY DID.
I DON'T THINK THERE IS ANYBODY
THAT WOULD DENY THAT.
>> SOMETHING THAT MIGHT HOLD ME
BACK FROM THIS GAME IS I'M
EXTREMELY HOW ABOUT.
I EITHER LOVE YOU OR HATE YOU
AND YOU'LL PROBABLY KNOW.
I KNOW IT WASN'T SMART TO GO OFF
ON JIM IN FRONT OF EVERYONE.
IT'S FACT.
I DIDN'T DO WELL AT THE LAST
PART OF THE CHALLENGE.
I'M NOT GOING TO DENY THAT.
>> I'M NOT PUTTING YOUR NAME
DOWN.
I'M NOT.
>>
>> I WON'T PUT YOURS DOWN.
>> YOU'RE A NICE PERSON AND YOUR
HEART IS HERE.
>> HAVING STARTED THE GAME IN A
WAY THAT WAS PRETTY EMOTIONAL, I
THINK THERE'S A REAL POSSIBILITY
THAT THE TRIBE IS GOING TO LOOK
AT ME AND SAY THAT OUTBREAK
BEING EMOTIONAL LIKE THAT IS A
LIABILITY FOR THE TRIBE.
BUT I'M HOPING PEOPLE WILL BASE
THEIR DECISIONS ON, YOU KNOW,
TODAY FORWARD, ESPECIALLY WITH
THE CONFLICT TODAY WITH SEMHAR
AND JIM.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
THE REALITY IS SHE DESERVES TO
GO.
>> YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT SEMHAR?
>> YEAH.
SHE SCREWED UP THE CHALLENGE,
WHICH SHE SHOULD NOT HAVE
VOLUNTEERED TO DO.
>> YEAH.
MY GUT TELLS ME RIGHT NOW THAT
THE TIMING OF TRIBAL COUNCIL
BEING SO CLOSE AND THEN THE
ARGUMENT AT CAMP THAT IT MIGHT
BE SEMHAR GOING HOME.
SO IT'S SEMHAR?
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M PUTTING DOWN.
>> OKAY.
>> I JUST THINK THAT FOR THIS
FIRST VOTE, LIKE, WE REALLY NEED
TO THINK HARD.
I DON'T-- I DON'T NECESSARILY
THINK BECAUSE SHE MESSED UP ON
THIS CHALLENGE THAT SHE SHOULD
GO, I REALLY DON'T.
>> REALLY?
>> I THINK IT'S GOING TO BE A
HARD SELL TO THE WHOLE GROUP.
>> LISTEN TO THIS.
JUST FROM THE PERSPECTIVE OF
TRYING TO KEEP A STRONG TRIBE
HAVING YOU THREE GIRLS IS
ACTUALLY AN ADVANTAGE FOR US.
DAWN, I THINK SHE DID REALLY,
REALLY WELL.
>> TOTALLY.
>> SHE'S STRONG.
YOU KNOW, I HATE TO SAY IT, BUT
COCHRAN IS--
>> I KNOW.
>> HE'S IN THE MIDDLE.
AND HE'S NOT GOING TO BE, LIKE,
OUR STRONG PLAYER.
HE'S JUST NOT AS COORDINATED.
HE'S JUST NOT ATHLETIC.
YOU GOT COCHRAN ON ONE HAND THAT
REALLY IS NOT SHOWING MUCH IN
THE PHYSICALITY SENSE AND YOU'VE
GOT SEMHAR ON THE OTHER.
SHE BASICALLY BLEW THE CHALLENGE
FOR US, BUT IT'S NOT FAIR TO
BLAME SEMHAR IN THIS SITUATION.
IT TAKES BALLS TO STEP UP.
AND SHE DID TAKE A CHANCE.
>> BUT SHE-- I'D RATHER HAVE
SOMEBODY NOT STEP UP THAN
SOMEBODY WHO IS SO UNAWARE OF
THEIR INABILITIES.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> SEMHAR KNOWS SHE'S ON THE
CHOPPING BLOCK TONIGHT.
HERE'S MY CONCERN, OZZY WANTS
HER AROUND FOR A REASON AND IT'S
ROUND ONE AND IT SCARES ME THAT
HE ALREADY HAS A REASON TO KEEP
HER AROUND.
>> LET'S JUST THINK ABOUT THIS
REALLY CAREFULLY.
I MEAN--
>> I'M CONCERNED THAT OZZY MIGHT
GET IN AN ALLIANCE WITH ALL THE
GIRLS.
HE HAS CHARM.
I COULD SEE THAT HAPPENING.
BUT SEMHAR IS PRETTY MUCH
USELESS.
HER BODY IS MESMERIZING BUT IT'S
NOT HYPNOTIZING AND IT BLOWS MY
MIND THAT OZZY MIGHT BE ACTUALLY
FACTORING IN THAT SNUGGLE
FACTOR.
IT'S A MILLION-DOLLAR DECISION.
>> I'M ON YOUR SIDE.
I WANT TO SEE YOU STAY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> THE HARD DECISION IS BETWEEN
YOU AND BETWEEN COCHRAN.
>> IF YOU WANNA STAY HERE, YOU
HAVE TO DO SOME WORK.
YOU GOTTA DO SOME POLITICKING,
LIKE, SERIOUSLY.
>> IT'S BETWEEN COCHRAN AND I,
BASICALLY.
>> WHO'S GOING FOR COCHRAN?
>> I DON'T KNOW, EXACTLY.
SO I SUGGESTED KEEP ME.
COCHRAN JUST SEEMS TO BE A HUGE
FAN OF THE GAME BUT NOT
NECESSARILY PLAYING THE GAME.
>> YEAH.
>> SO, SAD TO SAY, I'M TRYING TO
GET PEOPLE TO VOTE HIM OFF.
>> WHO ARE YOU GOING WITH, ME OR
COCHRAN?
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY.
IT'S NOT YOU.
>> I REALLY APPRECIATE THAT.
>> THEY WANT YOU GONE.
LIKE, OZZY THINKS THAT YOU'RE
THE BEST-- OZI THINKS YOU'RE THE
BEST TARGET RIGHT NOW.
>> WHY?
>> THE WAKEST.
>> I'M NOT THE WEAKEST, THOUGH.
>> I WENT TO BAT FOR YOU.
>> WHO DOES OZZY THINK IS GOING
TO VOTE ME OUT AND BE
SUCCESSFUL?
>> HE'S JUST PUSHING FOR IT.
HE'S TRYING TO SEE HOW MUCH
CLOUD CLOUT HE HAS PROBABLY
RIGHT NOW.
>> MY ACHILLES' HEEL IS
CRIPPLING INSECURITY AND ANXIETY
AND IT'S HEARTBREAKING TO LEARN
THAT APPARENTLY OZZY IS SAYING
I'M THE WEAKEST PERSON AND THEY
SHOULD GET RID OF ME FOR THAT.
>> IT'S CRAZY.
>> IT'S EXPLICITLY BEEN STATED
THAT I'M THE TARGET.
SO RIGHT NOW I'M ON HIGH-ALERT,
PARANOIA MODE AND EXTREMELY
DEPRESSED.
>> IT'S NOT YOU.
DO NOT GET PARANOID.
IT'S NOT YOU.
I WOULD TELL YOU.
I WOULD SAY YOU'RE IN TROUBLE
AND I DON'T MEAN MAYBE.
>> THAT'S WHAT I'VE BEEN
THINKING.
TO BE THE FIRST PERSON KICKED
OFF IN THE FIRST PERSON WHEN I'M
ON A TRIBE WITH PAPA BEAR AND
SEMHAR AND ALL THESE GIRLS?
IT'S LIKE, THIS IS INSULTING.
>> IT'S NOW NOT YOU.
THEY LIKE YOU.
THEY SAY YOU'RE FUN TO BE
AROUND.
>> YEAH, BUT PEOPLE DON'T LIKE A
FUN GUY ALL THE TIME.
"SURVIVOR" IS NOT MEANT TO BE A
COMEDY ROUTINE.
THIS IS A NIGHTMARE.
IT STARTED OUT AS A DREAM, BUT
IT REALLY IS A NIGHTMARE NOW.
>> THE GAME MAKES YOU PARANOID.
>> MY NAME IS GOING TO APPEAR.
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF HOW MANY
TIMES.
TRIBAL COUNCIL TONIGHT IS GOING
TO SUCK.
I'M NOT LOOKING FORWARD TO IT.
I'M PROBABLY GOING TO HEAR, "THE
TRIBE HAS SPOKEN."
MY TORCH IS GOING TO BE SNUFFED.
IT'S A
>> Jeff: BEHIND EACH OF US IS
A TORCH.
GO AHEAD, GRAB A TORCH, APPROACH
THE FLAME AND GET FIRE.
THIS IS PART OF THE RITUAL OF
TRIBAL COUNCIL BECAUSE IN THIS
GAME, FIRE REPRESENTS YOUR LIFE.
WHEN YOUR FIRE'S GONE, SO ARE
YOU, WITH A SLIGHT EXCEPTION,
REDEMPTION ISLAND, WHICH WE WILL
TALK ABOUT.
OKAY, DAWN, HAS THERE BEEN MUCH
TALK ABOUT REDEMPTION ISLAND AND
WHAT THAT MIGHT BE LIKE TO GO
THERE ALONE?
>> OH, YEAH.
I THOUGHT TODAY ABOUT IS
EVERYBODY PREPARED TO DO IT?
YOU KNOW, I THINK THE FIRST
THREE DAYS YOU'RE SO FOCUSED ON
GETTING THE SHELTER AND GETTING
WATER, MAKING SURE YOU'RE
PREPPED FOR THE FIRST CHALLENGE.
IT'S HARD WITH NINE PEOPLE.
SO, SOLO, TOUGH.
>> Jeff: HOW BAD DID IT GET
THESE FIRST TWO DAYS?
>> DAY ONE AND DAY TWO I FELT
LIKE I DIDN'T KNOW WHO I WAS
ANYMORE AND I THINK THAT'S
BECAUSE EVERYTHING THAT'S
FAMILIAR TO ME IS GONE AND I
LOST A LOT OF CONFIDENCE WITH
ALL THAT CHANGE.
THERE'S NOTHING ABOUT MY LIFE
HERE THAT IS LIKE MY LIFE AT
HOME.
>> Jeff: YOU LOST A LOT OF
CONFIDENCE IN YOURSELF.
>> I CRIED, YEAH, AND I'M REALLY
STRONG.
I DON'T KNOW THAT I CRY VERY
OFTEN IN MY LIFE EVER.
AND I EVEN CONFIDED IN OZZY TO
GET SOME BEARING AND GET MY LEGS
BACK AND IT'S KIND OF LIKE I HAD
THE FLU AND IT'S GONE.
>> Jeff: ELYSE, WHO ELSE HERE
DO YOU THINK MIGHT BE WORRIED
BECAUSE THEY'VE JUST GOTTEN OFF
TO A ROUGH START?
>> I THINK HONESTLY, I THINK
SEMHAR IS CONCERNED.
BECAUSE OF THE WAY THE CHALLENGE
WENT TODAY AND BECAUSE OF THE
CONVERSATION THAT WE ALL HAD
WHEN WE GOT BACK TO CAMP.
>> Jeff: JIM, WHAT WAS THE
CONVERSATION YOU HAD BACK AT
CAMP SURROUNDING SEMHAR?
>> I'M A COMPETITOR.
I'M GOING TO COMPETE AT EVERY
SINGLE EVENT, AND I HATE LOSING.
YOU KNOW, SHE WANTED TO GO OUT
AND PROVE HERSELF AND DO IT AND
SHE WAS VERY CONFIDENT IN HER
ABILITIES, AND I THINK THE ONLY
PEOPLE THAT ARE GOOD LOSERS ARE
PEOPLE THAT ARE GOOD AT LOSING.
>> Jeff: WHITNEY, WAS THERE
ANY PART OF YOU THINKING I'M
GLAD IT'S NOT ME?
>> YEAH, OBVIOUSLY, THE
ATTENTION IS NOT ON ME.
BUT ACTUAL HE, I THOUGHT I
DEFINITELY CAN DO IT BUT WHEN
SHE WAS SO VOCAL ABOUT HER
ABILITIES, NO ONE ELSE REALLY
HAD A CHANCE TO JUMP IN AND SAY,
"YEAH, I CAN DO THIS."
>> Jeff: SEMHAR YOU'RE SHAKING
YOUR HEAD BACK AND FORTH.
>> I UNDERSTAND THIS GAME.
I KNOW I'M SAFE IF I DIDN'T STEP
UP, AND I TAKE COMPLETE
RESPONSIBILITY FOR TAKING ON
SOMETHING THAT WAS OUT OF MY
LEAGUE.
HOWEVER, I KNOW I GOT HURT.
I KNOW I'M GOING TO GIVE IT ALL
THAT I'VE GOT.
>> Jeff: OZZY, WOULD YOU
RATHER PLAY THIS GAME WITH
SOMEBODY WHO HAS THE GUTS, LIKE
SEMHAR DID, TO SAY I THINK I CAN
DO THIS OR PLAY WITH A GUY THAT
SAYS, BETTER YOU THAN ME."
>> PHILOSOPHICALLY BETTER TO
STEP UP WITH SOMEBODY WHO HAS
THE HEART TO STEP UP AND TRY.
TO HANAS YOUR PASSION AND DO
WHAT EVERYONE ELSE THINKS IS
IMPOSSIBLE AND SAY, "I CAN DO
THIS," IT'S A HUGE, HUGE
ADVANTAGE IN THIS GAME.
>> DAWN, WHO ELSE MIGHT BE
WORRIED JUDGING FROM THE FIRST
TWO DAYS?
>> MAYBE COCHRAN.
BASED ON JUST STRENGTH.
I THINK THAT HE MIGHT BE ANOTHER
TARGET.
>> I KNOW HER RATIONALE BECAUSE
YOU LOOK AT MY GLASSES YOU, LOOK
AT MY SWEATER VEST, YOU LOOK AT
MY PALE SKIN, IT'S EASY TO SAY
HE'S ONE OF THE WEAKEST PURPOSE.
I HUMMED THROUGH THE NET.
NOBODY SEEMS TO CARE ABOUT THAT.
MAYBE I HAD A SNAFU CLIMBING UP
THE WALL BUT IT LASTED HALF A
SECOND.
>> Jeff: WHAT HAPPENED GOING
UP THE WALL?
>> WAS THAT A NOTICEABLE THING?
>> YES.
>> I CAN ANSWER THAT.
>> Jeff: MARK ANTHONY.
>> CALL ME PAPA BEAR.
>> Jeff: PAPA BEAR?
>> THAT'S MY NICKNAME.
I LIKE IT, DON'T WORRY.
>> Jeff: SO, PAPA BEAR, YOU
CAN ANSWER THE QUESTION OF WHAT
HAPPENED GOING UP THE WALL.
>> FOR TWO SECONDS HE GOT
CONFUSED AND SAID, "WHAT DO I
DO, WHAT DO I DO?"
ME AND OZZY FLIPPED HIM OVER THE
WALL.
YOU HISITATED.
>> SO IT WAS LIKE FATAL?
IT WAS A FATAL MISTAKE?
>> NO, BUT YOU MACK A DECISION
AND GO WITH IT, YOU DON'T STOP.
AND SOMETIMES YOU NEED
CORRECTION.
I'M SORRY.
>> Jeff: SO, SEMHAR, SUDDENLY
THE ATTENTION HAS SHIFTED OFF OF
YOU ON TO COCHRAN.
YOU HAVE TO BE LOVING THIS?
>> WAS IT A SLIGHT RELIEF THE
FACT THAT SOME PEOPLE SAW
COCHRAN AS A WEAKER LINK THAN
ME?
I'M NOT GOING IT LIE--
>> HAS ANYBODY SAID THAT
DIRECTLY, THOUGH?
>> YOUR NAME HAS COME UP.
I WILL SAY THAT.
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF VOTE AT
THIS POINT.
ONLY TIME WILL TELL.
>> YOU BETTER NOT SAY, "IT IS
TIME TO VOTE" RIGHT NOW.
AM I ALLOWED TO INTERJECT.
>> Jeff: COCHRAN, WE WILL SIT
HERE AS LONG AS YOU GUYS WANT
TO.
THIS IS YOUR TRIBAL COUNCIL.
>> I DIDN'T WANT TO GET THIS
EARLY INTO KIND OF SAYING PEOPLE
AREN'T WORKING HARD, BUT I
THINK-- I'M BLANKING--
>> SEMHAR.
I'M SORRY.
I'M SO SORRY.
I'M NERVOUS RIGHT NOW.
IT'S NO INDICATION WHAT I THINK
OF YOU.
YOU STAND BY THE POT FOR, I
DON'T KNOW, LIKE, 10 HOURS A
DAY, AND IT'S AN IMPORTANT JOB
BUT I DON'T THINK IT'S THE MOST
PHYSICALLY STRENUOUS ONE.
>> I MAKE SURE EVERYBODY HAS
TOOTHBRUSHES --
>> YOU FIND A COUPLE STICKS.
I'M SAYING IT'S NOT A HUGE JOB.
>> IT'S A JOB NO ONE HAS TO ASK
ME TO DO.
THAT'S THE POINT I'M TRYING TO
MAKE.
THAT'S ALL.
>> YOU MAKE IT SOUND LIKE I'M
WANDERING AROUND UNTIL YOU TELL
ME TO GET WOOD.
THIS IS THE GROWING PERIOD.
I'M BUILDING A KNOWLEDGE BASE.
I OPENED MY FIRST COCONUT.
I WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN ABLE TO DO
THAT TWO DAYS AGO.
I'M NOT HAVING TO PERPETUALLY
HAVING TO RELEARN THINGS.
I DO IT ONCE AND LEARN IT.
>> Jeff: ARE YOU A LEARNER MY
NATURE?
>> THIS IS A CULMINATION OF THE
PASSION FOR THIS GAME AND THE
POSSIBILITY OF BEING THE FIRST
PERSON KICKED OFF IS
HEARTBREAKING AND MORTIFY.
>> Jeff: IF YOU SURVIVE
TONIGHT'S VOTE, WHAT NEEDS TO
CHANGE TOMORROW MORNING?
>> I WILL DO WHATEVER HAS TO BE
DONE AROUND CAMP.
I WILL BE YOUR JEANIE IN A
BOTTLE.
YOU WON'T HAVE TO RUB.
I'M CAPITOL HILL OUT AND DO IT.
YOU WILL SEE A WHOLE NEW
COCHRAN.
MY EYES ARE OPEN TO THE
PERCEPTION OF ME AND I'LL TAKE
THAT INTO ACCOUNT AND I DON'T
THINK SEMHAR HAS THAT SAME
PASSION FOR BEING PART OF
"SURVIVOR."
>> CAN I-- WHENEVER YOU'RE DONE?
>> YOU CAN GO AHEAD.
>> THEY THINK WORKS AGAINST YOU,
TO BE HONEST WITH YOU.
I THINK YOU'RE SO MERMERRIZED BY
THE GAME THAT YOU FORGET HOW.
THE IT IS TO BE THAT PERSON WHO
IS JUST WORKING.
>> I DON'T THINK IT NECESSARILY
SHOULD BE BASED ON WHAT'S
HAPPENED SO FAR.
>> WHAT DO WE BASE IT ON THEN?
>> IT HAS TO BE BASED ON WHAT
HAS HAPPENED SO FAR.
>> DOES IT HAVE TO BE?
>> IT HAS TO BE.
WE HAVE ONLY KNOWN YOU FOR THREE
DAYS.
WE ONLY HAVE KNOWN EVERYBODY FOR
THREE DAYS.
YOU HAVE A SMALL WINDOW TO GET
TO KNOW PEOPLE, YOU KNOW?
>> Jeff: IT SEEMS PRETTY CHEER
AT THIS POINT THAT IT IS SEMHAR
OR COCHRAN GOING HOME.
WITH THAT, IT IS TIME TO VOTE.
PAPA BEAR, YOU'RE UP.
>> I'M REALLY SORRY, BUT
HOPEFULLY THIS MIGHT MAKE YOU
STEP UP EVEN MORE.
>> I THINK IT'S PRETTY OBVIOUS
WHY I'M VOTING IF YOU YOU.
YOU'VE QUESTIONED MY
INTELLIGENCE.
YOU'VE QUESTIONED MY COMMITMENT
TO THIS GAME AND YOU'VE MADE ME
QUESTION WHY I SHOULD BE HERE
ANY LONGER SO I CAN'T TAKE IT.
>> Jeff: I'LL GO TALLY THE
VOTES.
ONCE THE VOTE ARE READ THE
DECISION IS FINAL.
THE PERSON VOTED OUT WILL BE
ASKED TO LEAVE THE TRIBAL
COUNCIL AREA IMMEDIATELY.
I'LL READ THE VOTES.
FIRST VOTE, COCHRAN.
SEMHAR.
THAT'S TWO VOTES SEMHAR, ONE
VOTE COCHRAN.
SEMHAR.
THREE VOTE SEMHAR, ONE VOTE
COCHRAN.
SEMHAR.
THAT'S FOUR VOTE SEMHAR.
FIRST PERSON VOTED OUT OF
"SURVIVOR: SOUTH PACIFIC,"
SEMHAR.
THAT'S FIVE.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU NEED TO BRING ME YOUR TORCH.
SEMHAR, THE TRIBE HAS SPOKEN.
YOU WILL HAVE A CHANCE TO GET
BACK IN THIS GAME.
GRAB YOUR TORCH, HEAD TO
REDEMPTION ISLAND.
>> I SHOULD HAVE TAUGHT HER HOW
TO MAKE A FIRE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Jeff: WELL, IT APPEARS THAT
YOU MADE THE DECISION TO BELIEVE
THAT A PERSON CAN IMPROVE.
LET'S HOPE IT GOES FOR THE
ENTIRE TRIBE.
GRAB YOUR TORCHES.
HEAD BACK TO CAMP.
GOOD NIGHT.
f: AND BRANDON'S SECT
WEIGHS HEAVY.
>> I FELT LIKE I WAS BEING
DISHONEST WITH COACH.
>> Jeff: WHEN AWAKENS THE
DRAGON SLAYER.
>> I THINK HE HAS DEMONS
Captioning brought to you by
Survivor Productions, CBS,
and Ford.
Drive one.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
THERE'S GOING TO BE AN APOF
SS WHIPPING.
>> IF YOU LOSE YOUR DUAL, YOU
WILL BE OUT OF THE GAME AND MUST
LEAVE REDEMPTION